What's wrong, Astro?
>> I had that same nightmare again where
two monogous homosexual tunes break into
my house and beat me up. My head's still
foggy and hurts from where they hit me
that I still can't recall who exactly
they were. We'll find out who hurt you
last week. But remember, the doctor said
not to move around too much since you're
still medicated.
>> You're getting I core all over my
bathroom.
>> I'm sorry. I'll clean it up.
>> Golly, we can do that later. Let's go to
the kitchen. The Easter Tunes will be
here soon, and they said they are going
to make you some beans on toast.
Breakfast is served.
>> Flutter, why do you got to act like a
[__] The Easter tunes are let out of
Dandy's basement for one month of the
year, and you can't even pretend to like
flights cooking for one day.
>> When we're locked up in there most of
the year, we can't afford anything
except beans. Please understand. Well,
as long as Astro likes it, that's all
that matters.
>> Dandy, we heard Astro had a hard week.
I'm going to put on a magic show this
morning with all our friends to try and
cheer him up.
>> That's nice. Me and the other Easter
tunes are setting up shop to sell our
Easter eggs until noon. Do you think you
could stop by?
>> Maybe after I'm done with my magic show
I just told you about. That'll be taking
up most of my morning [__] For my next
and final magic trick, I'm going to need
an assistant. Pick me. Pick me. Pick me.
>> Oh, pick me, Dandy.
>> I pick Astro.
>> This isn't fair. Astro was your
assistant for every single magic trick
>> because this magic show is all for him.
He was just let out of the hospital for
like a week, so it's his day.
>> What even happened to you, Astro? Oh, I
was
>> Astro, shut up. I tell stories better. A
couple of crazies broke into his house
in the middle of the night and beat
Astro's ass and stole all his expensive
[__] like cooking utensils and his
Nintendo Switch.
>> Who would do such a heartless thing?
>> I don't know, Roger. You tell us. You're
the detective I brought on for the case,
but you've been sitting in my house all
weekend eating my macaroni salad like a
fat [__]
>> I don't just sit all day. The calories
and nutrients I absorb from your
macaroni go straight to my brain and fat
butt, and that's what I use to drive my
search. There were two broken windows,
so we know it had to be not one, but two
asalants working together. One's ass was
far bigger than the others based off the
cracks around one of the windows where
they struggled to get their butt cheeks
through. A cookie was lying in the
middle of the room with a trail of
crumbs behind it. Naturally, it could
have rolled off a counter when Astro was
attacked. But I think what's more likely
is that one of the attackers had rolled
the cookie out into the hallway themsel
to lure Astro out of the bathroom while
he was taking a fat [__] Lastly, there
was eye core all over the living room.
So, I believe at least one of the tunes
that night had gone twisted, which would
explain how they were able to overpower
Astro, who could have easily fought back
since he had four arms and [__]
>> I want to be Dy's magic assistant at
least once. It's no fun that the rest of
us just have to sit here. Well, damn
[__] the door is right over there. You
can leave. I don't want to leave cuz all
my friends are here.
>> Dandy, it's okay. I don't have to
participate in all the magic tricks. It
will be fun to watch at least one of
them from the sidelines.
>> For my final trick, Sprout, we're going
to handcuff our hands together. But
that's gay. It would almost be like
we're holding hands. Do you want to do
it or not? Okay, listen. I'm going to
give you a key in your right hand.
Switch it off to your left hand when the
others aren't looking. And I'm going to
tap your right hand with my magic wand
to make it look like it disappeared.
Then switch the key back so we make it
look like I brought it back with magic.
This isn't magic at all. Are you all
hearing this [__] Hey, Astro, watch
this.
>> I don't know if you should be doing
that.
>> That hurt. Be amazed, [__] as the
key has magically faded into
nothingness.
>> Holy [__]
>> Now I will make the key reappear before
your very eyes.
>> What did you do? You ruined my trick.
Oh, are you really crying? I just wanted
to be a goofy goober. I I didn't know
this whole thing meant so much to you,
dweeb. Of course, it means a lot to me.
What else do I have?
>> I have a key copy machine at home. I'll
take the pieces and make a quick copy.
>> Ah, I'm going home, too. It's been like
8 hours since I let Finn outside to take
a piss out of his tiny balls. It was a
fun magic show, but I think I'm going to
go home and take a nap. The hospital
meds are still wearing off.
>> Well done, Sprout. Your lustful desire
to inconvenience me for 5 seconds has
inconvenience the both of us for the
next 45 minutes. Daddy needs to go poop.
Roger will be back in less than an hour.
So, Daddy is going to wait. You wouldn't
be telling V, Shelly, or Astro they'd
have to hold it. You're only telling me
that because you don't like me. Maybe
so, but you have to deal with it. No,
I'm stronger than you. Ah, stop it.
Hurry up. A tune can't control the speed
at which poop falls out of their butt. I
promised the Easter tunes that I would
stop by their Easter egg stand outside
Walmart this morning and buy some of
their eggs. Well, okay, but I got to
wipe first. Hand me the toilet paper.
Bass C told me that her and the Easter
tunes are trying to sell enough Easter
eggs so they can buy some bicycles and
ride around together before they are
locked back up in my basement at the end
of the month with all the other holiday
tunes. They want to get a feel of what
it's like to be free to go wherever they
want. Just a few short days. I'm going
to pop all the wheels though as soon as
they buy them to make sure their bikes
only have limited time usage because I
can't have them just riding away and
escaping Garden View. I'm not fast
enough to catch a tune on a bike with
proper wheels, but I bet I could catch
up to one on a bike if their wheels are
popped. Dork. I literally don't care
about any of the information you just
told me.
Do you think 40 bucks would be enough to
make Bass C and her friends happy? What
are you going to do with $40 worth of
eggs? Well, some of them are going to
you. You You're going to buy me Easter
eggs even though you hate me? It's not
cuz I like you or anything. I just don't
want to take so many home myself.
>> Dandy Sprout. Good morning.
D anything you like. As you can see, the
eggs are all sorted by color.
>> What kind of candy did you put in them?
>> No candy this year. They're just painted
hardboiled eggs.
>> Where do you even get all these? There's
no chickens in my basement.
>> Oh, you know, Egg Sun just pushes them
out for us.
Can I get just a big box of blue eggs? I
wanted to get red ones so I can glue
grass to the top and make them look like
strawberries. Just because we're
handcuffed together, it doesn't mean we
have to buy the same color of eggs.
Fine. Why are you giving me an attitude?
You're getting what you want and I'm
still paying. [__] I just noticed it's
700 a.m. I need to go home and open the
bakery. Just get Cozmo to do that. I
can't. Cosmo is a twink. They can't do
anything by themselves. Well, I don't
want to walk all the way across town
with you. Fly, come here for a sec.
Bast the Halloween. They're doing
another driveby. Coco, get down, [__]
>> FLIGHT, your fat cheeks. Clapper 67.
>> Sylvester, your sir claps a lot.
What are the odds this would be the
case? I thought we agreed to meet behind
the Walmart so as not to draw suspicion.
>> Oh, I thought you weren't going to be
here for another hour.
>> My Halloween pals wanted to remind the
Easter tunes who it was that runs this
side of Garden View. I wouldn't have
participated in the driveby if I knew
you were Fat Cheeks Clapper 67.
>> We can go behind the building now if you
want. I'll just have to tell the other
Easter tunes that I'll be stepping away
for a bit.
>> You'll be getting a whole lot more than
those coins. sexy tune boy if you do all
the things you promised you'd do over
text
>> flight I don't fully get what's going on
here but if it's what I think you can't
be doing this especially on Easter
Sunday
>> it's fine Jesus doesn't care what goes
up my ass as long as I'm on my knees and
keep my wings clasped together in prayer
at least that's what I tell myself
>> so are we making this deal or not I do
not have all day
>> flight
>> it's entrepreneurial God made me gay so
it's not bad for me to make it a service
what he wants I'm naturally gifted in
certain boy-on boy activities and a boy
is willing to compensate me for those
gifts. Who would I be to deny the
universe?
>> Is though done spiraling or is there
more for thee to bestow upon us?
>> Okay, let me recompose myself for a
second. Reinvent the vibe. So, Mr. Big
Strong Ghost Knight, how much are we
talking?
>> That depends on how much of me you can
take.
>> Let's take a guess first and say until
you're exhausted and can't go no more.
I like that answer.
>> Flight.
>> Do you think I like doing this? You're
the star of the show, Dandy. You're free
to do whatever you want all the time. I
don't have the luxury. We The Easter
tunes don't have the luxury. So, it's
you who's putting me in this position.
Just because I'm an Easter tune, you
lock me up in your basement for 11
months out of the year with three ugly
tunes who are an old man, a rabbit, and
a flower basket. Right now, I only have
one reason to live. I want ghost.
That's not even mentioning my sister on
the outside with no arms, can't talk,
and is totally talentless. She has no
job. I have to provide for her. And
selling Easter eggs outside of the
Walmart only does so little at getting
her ass proper food on the table.
>> You know, I was trying to be nice, but
I'm just going to say it. Read my
autobiography. It's $799.
It costs so much because it doubles as
an audio book. Close your legs and open
a Bible.
>> With what arms am I supposed to read
your stupid book with? The arms God
forgot to give me.
>> Flight. All I want is for you to get
into heaven like me. The path you're on
now is not it.
>> Dandy, if you're going to be there, I'm
afraid I'm content with missing out.
>> So then, my beloved flight, shall we go
back to my place and consumate our souls
to eternal damnation?
Heat.
flight.
>> Just because we're tied together doesn't
mean I've got to stop living my life.
>> No, no. It's just that kind of time with
a tune should be special. I shouldn't be
there. I got to wait for Sprout to come
back.
>> I can't get my shirt off cause of the
cuffs.
>> Just keep it there. I'll make sure it
doesn't fall down.
>> So, is Dandy just going to watch? Is
that his thing?
>> I won't look if you don't want me to,
but I can't leave.
>> Okay, so how do we do this?
>> What do you mean?
>> You know, even though I talk a big game
over text, I've never done this before.
>> I've been wanting to ask for the last 20
seconds. Do you like have nipples or is
it like under your fur?
>> Oh, I don't know if butterflies have
nipples. I never bothered to check. No.
>> Sylvester, what's wrong? Why are you
crying?
>> Forgive me, Flight. It's just It's been
forever since I opened up to someone
like this.
>> Asking about my nipples is opening up.
>> When I fell out of the car during the
driveby, the Halloween tunes never even
came back for me for being my friends. I
just thought they cared about me more.
It's been a long time since someone
treated me kindly like you.
>> Oh, okay. Well, you know, Sylvester, we
all know what it's like to be a sad tune
from time to time.
>> My sister Connie hits me when she gets
drunk.
>> Okay, I don't know how to respond to
that.
>> Ah, [__] Eclipse, he brought another
one home. Cover Gord's eyes.
>> He what? Cheater. Cheater. Cheater.
Pumpkin eater. You invited me here so we
could do a practice run for our future
marriage and honeymoon.
>> What is the pumpkin baby talking about?
>> Is that an Easter tune and dandy? We go
out for 10 minutes and you pick up the
two of the town [__]
>> Just one. Dandy only likes to watch.
>> Sprout, is your store open yet? I want
to buy a carrot cake for Dandy. What are
all those tunes doing in cages above
your bakery? It's a long story, but
basically a little while back, I caught
them trying to break into my bakery to
steal [__] and blotshot them all with a
gun. We thought they were all dead and
we buried them in the Garden View
Cemetery. But because we forgot tunes
can't really die, they managed to crawl
out of the dirt a couple days later. So
instead, we put them up in these cages
so that people can spit on them when
they walk by.
>> When will we be let out of our
confinement?
>> Stop talking.
>> Sprout, I've got something important to
tell you.
>> It better be about why Toodles is out of
her cage. Because I was making a copy of
Dandy's key, I had to get an extra set
of eyes on the case. The one where a
couple of tunes broke into Sprout's
house and beat his ass. Tell Mr. Seedley
what we discovered. Toodles.
>> I measured the dimensions of the larger
of the two windows that was busted at
Astro's house. And I came to the
conclusion that the only two-minute
olive garden view with an ass so fat
that Astro's whole entire living room
would nearly busted open the way it did
is if it was none other than Cosmo who
tried pushing his cheeks through.
>> Sprout, do you know where your sexy cake
boy was last Friday evening?
>> Are you trying to accuse my bakery boy
toy of something nefirious just because
he's got a dump truck?
>> All signs are simply pointing to his fat
butt cheeks, my boy. If we can clear
him, we can move the case forward in
other directions.
>> What are you two talking about? Roger
here thinks he just made a pretty big
discovery, Cosmo.
>> Oh, really? What kind of discovery?
>> He thinks he caught you doing something
you weren't supposed to.
>> Best you keep to yourself, Roger. That's
safer.
>> It may be safer, but uncovering truths
is more rewarding.
>> Sure, Roger. Sure.
You are not to leave that cage again or
I'm going to hit you with the razle and
dazzle stick. I'm not above hitting a
child.
>> Oh, Roger. Did you make a copy of the
key?
>> Yes. Finally, after a full 13 minutes,
you shall be freed of your confinements.
>> At least somebody will shut up.
Finally, my wrist was starting to hurt.
Hey [__] what do you all say?
Instead of working the bakery, we go to
my strawberry house and dig our gay
little mouths into a batch of leftover
cupcakes I have sitting on my counter
from last night.
>> Cosmo, you're going to have to stay here
since we'll have customers soon. But I
know you were going to do that anyway
cuz you're a good [__]
So, we're alone now. Seems so. Why
didn't you go with the others for
cupcakes?
>> I wanted to ask you something, Cosmo.
>> Oh, what?
>> Last week when Astro was in the
hospital, you said you would visit him
and bring him cookies, but you never
did.
>> Oh, did I? I must have forgot.
>> Did you? Or did you just eat them all up
because you're fat?
Hey, you also weigh 600 lb.
So, it wasn't enough to break into his
house and beat his ass with rolling
pins. You just had to fill him with
false anticipation for cookies he was
never going to receive?
Do you take joy in toying with him?
Because Sprout ingrained that in you. Or
is it that between you bakery boys, you
are the real twisted one.
>> What do you mean by that?
Huh?
You hurt my pet. I thought all day about
whether or not I should hurt yours as
revenge. But why hurt the pet when I can
hurt the one pulling its leash?
This is my world. If I don't like a
tune, they don't have to exist. you
know, and I really, really don't like
you right now.
At the end of the day, Cosmo, all you
are is a baked good to satisfy my
cravings.
That's enough, Dandy.
Dandy,
>> where's Cosmo?
>> He's okay. I put both of you to sleep. I
knew Sprout is going to be mad at you if
he saw the hole in Cosmo's chest, so I
quickly made a chocolate cake and fixed
the hole using dollar store frosting.
>> Why didn't you let me unal alive him?
Because Cosmo is our friend,
>> Astro, he was the one who broke into
your house and brutalized you last week.
Him and Sprout.
>> Why didn't you just tell me?
>> When I realized it was them who did it,
I wanted to comfort you. But because
they hurt you so bad, you didn't
remember. And I didn't want to bring
those memories back. So, all I could
think to do was to get back at them.
>> Oh, but I didn't want you to know. I
mean, everyone knows I'm Garden View's
baddest [__] and I'm not ashamed to
have that side of me, but I don't want
you to see it because
>> because we're friends.
Because I know you love me, and I don't
want your feelings for me to be tainted
like that.
>> Oh, Dandy, nothing you could do would
make me love you any less.
>> What if I did on Alive Cosmo? There's no
way you would still be talking like this
if I did.
>> But you didn't. So why even worry about
that? I'm telling you right here, right
now, everything is fine.
What are you doing? You'll get wet
without my blanket.
>> You're the one who needs to wear it. You
don't want others to see your self harm
scars, do you? The rain looks like it's
going to pass quickly anyway.
>> Thanks for being considerate. But what I
meant was, why did you kiss me?
>> I I don't know. I just think maybe I
needed it.
>> Are you okay?
>> Not exactly. Dandy, do you remember how
me and the other Easter tunes set up an
Easter egg booth so we could all buy
bicycles?
>> Yeah.
>> Well, after they found out I shared a
bed with Sylvester, they refused to buy
me a bike because, as they put it, gay
tunes have no reason for outdoor
activities because because they do
enough riding in the bedroom.
>> Makes sense. You holiday tunes move
around these streets with gang
mentality, and you letting yourself be
penetrated by a rival holiday tune was
naturally going to make them reconsider
your position as an Easter tune. Who
cares if I want to be with a boy?
>> Well, the Easter tunes you just told us.
>> Hey, Flight, we changed our mind about
not buying you a bike. Look, we bought
you a cheap shitty one from the Goodwill
for like $5. We did you the pleasure of
taking the seat off because we know you
would prefer the peg going up your ass
while you ride. We measured it and it's
about the same as Sylvester's forearm,
so it should be a nice fit.
We're going to the arcade. Smell yell
later.
>> If you want, we will go to the arcade
with you.
>> You would?
>> We all know what it's like to be a sad
tune from time to time and how that can
quickly be fixed by spending time with
others. Ken, I see if Sylvester wants to
come. I don't see why not. Just make
sure you and the rest of the Easter
[__] are back in my basement by
Sunday evening since that's the end of
the month.
>> I hope you like me.
If you do, I like you, too.
Why don't you try me?
I'm lost when I'm with you.
I don't know if you sh
think about you late at night.
I'm wondering if this feeling
is
true.
I hope I'm more than just friends.
I hope you feel this, too.
I want to be with you.
What if you say no?
But what if you say yes I do?
Tired of laying low. I'm lost when I'm
with you.
I don't know if you shed this light.
Think about you late at night.
I'm wondering if this feeling
is
true.
Oh, hi. Did you like today's episode of
Dandy's World? Do you want to know how
you can get your name to show during the
credits with all the others? All you got
to do is slap my ass. Haha. Just
kidding. You just got to subscribe to
Tamers1 2345 over on Patreon. For as
little as $3, your name will always show
up in the credits to show you support
the good [__] And you can also find
gifts over there that came from this
episode and all the previous ones. While
you're there, tell tamers what tune you
want the next episode to be all about.
I am the best.
Heat.